WUILLIAMS GONZÁLEZ

Llanguihue, Chile · 987673748

Wuilliams.work@outlook.com · linkedin.com/in/wuilliams-gonz%C3%A1lez-53050b160
Proz: 2725019

EN-ES Translator, specialized in International Business, I also have a Spanish Language Degree, and currently studying an Associate degree in Computer Science. I can not only translate, but I also provide services of proofreading, editing, subtitling, videogame localization among others. I am dedicated to my translations, and I always accomplish the expectations of my clients.

EXPERIENCE

2018 - 2022

FREELANCE TRANSLATOR, CHILE PROPERTY SPA

Translator for books about geophysics. "Statistical Methods in the Atmospheric Sciences" by Daniel S. Wilks.

2019 - 2020

FREELANCE TRANSLATOR, INIA REMEHUE OSORNO

Translator/Editor for the website of the company.

2022

COFUNDER, FACTURY BAKERY SPA

First SME entrepreneurship venture. Manager.

2023

FREELANCE TRANSLATOR, BERBA

Different types of texts.

2024

FREELANCE TRANSLATOR AND CORRECTOR, IDISC INFORMATION

TECHNOLOGIES

Different types of texts.

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019

EN-ES TRANSLATOR, UNIVERSIDAD TECNOLÓGICA DE CHILE INACAP

EN-ES Translator specialized in International Business. **Top 5** best students in the program.

2024- PRESENT

ASSOCIATE DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, CFT ESTATAL LOS LAGOS

Specialized in Cibersecurity.

SKILLS

- Virtual Assistance and Customer Support
- Data entry post editing
- Videogame Localization
- Adaptability

- Advanced computer skills
- Research
- Communication
- Time Management

ACTIVITIES

- Volunteer in "Translator without Borders"
- Self-taught Java, CSS and HTML.
- Artificial Intelligence course I and II
 (AI)
- Self-taught Photoshop, Lightroom

HOBBIES

- Videogames and TCGs
- Technology
- Music

- Photography
- Coffee and barista
- Sports